Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We'll live in one another.
No!
Listen, Nami, the climb
attack is a weapon,
but you have to rely on a stronger
one to use it, your brain.
You've got to think to survive a battle.
Remember, your mind is the real weapon.
Right, think.
Let's see, I've got key
balls and cool balls.
All I need to do is take advantage of
their characteristics and combine them!
One last thing.
Tornado Tempo.
This is the centerpiece
of the whole weapon.
Tornado Tempo?
Okay, here's the deal.
As long as your enemy is human,
they won't be able to stand
after being struck by it.
But it's a last resort,
and you only get one shot.
If you miss, it's over.
If I miss, it's over.
Pay attention.
That little gadget of yours is
interesting, but it's not a weapon.
Here's some advice, sweetie.
If you can't use it to attack,
it's nothing more than a toy.
The day that thing can
be called a weapon is
the day you can finally
hurt someone with it.
Now.
Stop running.
If I don't do something quick,
I'm going to get skewered.
The only chance I've got is
that tornado tempo thing.
If I can do it...
Hey! Give that back!
Did you seriously think you
could kill me with this toy?
Oh, please.
A sweater can produce more
electricity than this little thing.
Well, we won't know unless I
try, so give it back to me!
Come on, think!
I have to distract her somehow so
she can't dodge the tornado tempo!
What do I have to work with?
Uh,
there are three different
types of air bubbles
in the extremely dry
weather of this country,
but that's all.
If only there was just a little
more moisture in the air.
Wait, moisture? That's it!
This thing has a rain technique!
RING TEMPLE!!!
Water tricks?
ROTATING STRINKLER!!!
Desperate.
No, I'm not!
I've got a plan, you'll see!
I don't think so.
I've had enough of your party tricks.
And speaking of parties,
time to end this one. Uh-oh!
Sea urchin stinger!
Now why don't you be a good
little girl for me and die?
If that had been me instead of the wall.
Oh, man.
Since you showed me something
interesting earlier,
it's only fair that I return the favor.
Now's my chance!
Hot
air rises while
absorbing moisture when
it collides with cold
air that's descending!
It rapidly cools and the
moisture gets It's frozen.
And then...
Now, Spike, Spike! Doping!
I told you your life was
over, didn't I? Spinner!
At least you've proven that you're
a first-class expert at something,
even if it is running away.
Oh, right, the air bubbles!
A cloud!
It's small, but it formed!
Just what are you babbling about?
It's still not large enough, though.
I've got to make it bigger!
Cool balls!
Heat ball!
I've had about enough of this!
Time to die!
Stinger, fall!
Tell me, are you prepared to die?
How about you?
You're just bluffing, girl.
Am I?
You're dead meat!
Today's forecast calls for pleasant weather
with stable humidity and mild winds.
However, a high-pressure system will be
moving in sometime during the afternoon.
This could create some strange
weather in one particular area,
so people in the vicinity
need to watch out for mirages.
And more importantly, for tornadoes.
This is the centerpiece
of the whole weapon,
but it's a last resort,
and you only get one shot.
If you miss, it's over.
If I miss, it's over.
A tornado watch has been issued!
Something the matter?
Oh dear, it looks like that left
leg of yours is pretty injured.
So much so, in fact, that
I doubt you could run away.
Sea Archen, stay back!
This is...
it's nothing.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Do you have any idea what kind
of pain she's been going through?
compared to Phoebe.
It doesn't matter if I lose a foot
or a leg or two or even an arm.
I don't care!
Now, take this tornado!
Tempo!
What?! What?! What?! What?! What?!
What have you done to me?!
Ah!
Oh!
Huh?
Oh, my God.
It worked.
I did it.
Who's that, Phoebe?
What is he talking about? Pluton?
What is that?
I don't have a clue.
Pluton.
According to legend, it can completely
obliterate an island with just one shot.
An ancient weapon whose
power rivals that of a god.
It's somewhere in this country,
but you already knew that,
didn't you, your highness?
An ancient weapon?
Alabasta has such a thing?
And father knew about it?
Perhaps it is a secret
passed down with the throne.
Acquiring Pluton has always been my goal.
With it,
this peaceful country
will become a military
power to be reckoned with under my rule.
Your rule?
You're not this country's monarch.
Oh, but I soon will be.
And once I'm on the throne,
it will be easy to bring all the
pirates in this area under my umbrella.
With such influence,
eventually I'll gain more power than
even the world government itself.
No one will dare cross me.
The world government would never
allow you to wield that much power.
You're right, they wouldn't.
So where is the Pluton? Tell me.
I don't know where you
heard that name, Crocodile,
but I don't have the slightest
idea as to where it could be found.
I'm not even certain it ever existed,
let alone if it's hidden in this country.
It could be a myth for all I know.
What you say probably
isn't a complete lie.
I have considered that
possibility for a while now,
that Pluton may have never existed.
There are those who believe it's just
a fable, but I believe that it's real.
What noisy incense.
I heard that King Cobra's been
crucified by crocodile up there.
We've got to save his majesty.
If we can break through those
doors, we can save the king.
How?
We can't do anything because of those
strange hands coming out from them.
It's impossible unless we find
a way to stop those things.
If my timing's correct, the rebel army
should break through the defenses?
and reach that square in
approximately 20 minutes,
where they'll clash with the royal forces.
And then, in just half an hour, at 4.30,
their battle will be interrupted by a bomb
I've ordered to be fired into the square.
Please don't, I'm begging you.
Oh, and it's no ordinary bomb!
But one so powerful it will destroy
everything within a five kilometer radius.
If you do that, everyone?
That's right.
No one from either the royal army
or the rebel forces will survive.
They'll be wiped out and
the battle will be over.
Aren't you happy?
You should be After all, you're the
one who wanted them to stop so badly.
Since I'll be ruling from this palace,
there's no need to blow it
up just to end their fight.
It's easier just to blow
both armies up instead.
This land's worth more than they are.
How can you be so callous toward them?
What did these people ever do
to you to deserve this, huh?
They have lives and families!
Princess, who cares?
You don't have to kill
them, crocodile! Princess!
Perhaps I'll change my mind if
the king answers another question?
There's a poneglyph in
this country, your majesty.
Where is it?
Poneglyph?
What are you talking about?
If you promise to spare them,
I'll tell you where it is?
I'll even show you!
Father?
Just what I'd expect from a king.
You're a wise man.
Enough!
I cannot take...
another second of this!
Let me show you the difference in
pride between your swords and mine.
Three-sword style, full needle,
spider, defense.
so basically your body is as hard as steel
unless i can cut steel i can't defeat you?
that would be correct smashing and
cutting attacks won't work on me!
well that bites doesn't
it i'm not capable of
cutting steel yet so i
guess there's only one
thing left to do and
what's that swordsman i'm
gonna learn how to cut
it right here and now!
really i've been waiting
for a challenge just like
this one i've been telling
myself for a while now
that it's time to take my
skills to the next level
when i defeat you mr one
i'll be the swordsman!
strong enough to cut through anything
including steel
huh
when you defeat me?
that's rich i hate to shatter
your delusions pirate but i
feel it's only fair to warn you
that ever since i gained dice
dice powers i've never been
scratched by those who call
themselves swordsmen you'll
soon see no enemy can defeat me!
oh i'm really scared save those
stories for your grandkids if
you live that long pal anyway
i don't know how many swordsmen
you've defeated but you've never
fought me before so you better
watch what you say big guy cuz
you're about to eat those words!
the only thing sharp
about you is your tongue.
all right fine i warned you!
you won't last that long!
look who's talking.
Oh, my God.
Tony?
Tiger?
I told you.
Well, I've got to admit, I'm surprised
you don't even have a single bruise.
This is the first time
this has ever happened.
No opponent of mine is standing
after an attack like that.
As true as that may be,
you've never fought against me before,
so who's eating their words now?
Oh, right.
This guy's entire body is a blade, so
his blades don't have a front or a back.
Sparkling danger!
This is crazy!
Goodbye!
When it comes to training, I've
done more than anyone else.
I've also been pushed to the
brink in plenty of bad situations,
but always succeeded.
But what is it that I
lack to beat this guy?
Sensei! Sensei!
Hmm?
Is it true there are swordsmen in this
world who can cut anything, even steel?
Well, is it?
Yes, it certainly is.
Now pay attention.
I want you to watch this
paper very carefully, Zoro.
Ha!
Sensei, you didn't even cut it.
Listen, Zoro, this is an
important lesson for you to learn.
There are swordsmen out there who
are capable of cutting nothing.
However, these same swordsmen
can also cut anything,
and that includes steel,
using the same sword.
The strongest swordsmen
in the world are able
to protect that which
they want to protect,
but also cut that which they want to cut.
Sword play that always
harms whatever it touches.
Well, Zoro, that's not real swordsmanship.
Do you understand?
Sensei, I'm going to be a
swordsman who can cut anything.
Zoro, were you listening at
all to what I was saying?
Well what are you waiting for
hurry up and attack me again?
You'll never win if all you do is defend!
Trust me pal there's
nothing i'd rather do more
right now than that but
my hands are a little Full
at the moment and it
wasn't a threat it was a
promise i'm gonna cut
steel and you're gonna die!
I highly doubt it she
won't be alive to see it?
Large or small i'll cut
everything into pieces.
Swordplay that cuts nothing.
What the hell did that mean?
Think.
Cut nothing but cut steel.
It doesn't make any sense at all.
Thrust and thrust.
That's the secret of powerful swordplay.
Atomic spawn!
You're not the only one who can cut!
You're really starting to piss me off.
The feelings mutual.
Perhaps we'd be evenly matched if I
were a pathetic swordsman, but I'm not.
My weapons are far
nastier than mere swords.
Take this one for example.
Spiral Hollow.
Geez, what are you?
An excavator?
An assassin, actually.
Sparks!
Just how fast are those blades spinning?
Oh, no!
However, I don't mind
being called an excavator.
Because I'm going to be
digging out your organs.
There's only one thing
left for you after defeat.
Death.
I'm surprised you're still alive.
I will not show my back to him.
What are you going to fight with?
Your hands?
Stop!
Break!
Die in peace.
I've had bad luck with stones today.
I wonder if the rest of them are okay.
That's impossible.
I cut him so many times.
Did he dodge all those falling stones?
Is that what I did?
Dodge them?
No.
I was just able to sense the
place where no stones would fall.
My swords.
One of them is underneath that stone.
I feel it.
What is he doing?
I've experienced this feeling before.
Everything goes quiet around me so
quiet i can hear my heartbeat so clearly.
Is this is this what it feels
like when you're close to death?
It was almost like like
those falling stones
gave me a hint as if
they were living things.
No, it wasn't a hint.
It was much clearer than that.
It was like... rhythm.
Could it be...
trees have their own rhythm?
So does soil.
Is that what it is?
This is an important
lesson for you to learn.
Zoro, there are swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
Does cutting nothing mean
hearing the rhythm of the things
around you if so is that how
one can Cut steel what the
hell did you do after a vicious
attack like that and all
the blood you've lost There's
no way you can still be alive.
I hear it.
His steel.
It has a rhythm.
Just like everything else around me.
Alright.
Fine.
When I'm done, you're going
to wish you stayed down.
Only one question remains.
Do I really have the ability to cut steel?
Well, there's only one way to find out.
You failed with three swords.
Can you defend yourself with only one?
I won't defend.
So you're prepared to die!
One-sword style, Lion
Strike, Atomic Splendor!
Thanks to you.
I've finally reached the next level.
I don't know how, but he learned how
to do it, just like he said he would.
Now that you've cut steel,
what's next for you, Diamonds?
No.
That'd be a waste.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Good luck.